const questions = [
    {
        question: "Apa nama tim balap binaan PT Astra Honda Motor?",
        optionA: "Astra Racing Team",
        optionB: "Honda Racing Team",
        optionC: "Astra Honda Racing Team",
        optionD: "Astra Honda Racing",
        correctOption: "optionC",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Berapa jumlah pebalap Astra Honda Racing Team di tahun 2021?",
        optionA: "11 Pebalap",
        optionB: "15 Pebalap",
        optionC: "13 Pebalap",
        optionD: "12 Pebalap",
        correctOption: "optionD",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question: "Dimana saja pebalap Astra Honda Racing Team akan berlaga?",
        optionA: "Kejuaraan Eropa",
        optionB: "Kejuaraan Eropa, Asia dan Nasional",
        optionC: "Kejuaraan Nasional",
        optionD: "Kejuaraan Asia dan Nasional",
        correctOption: "optionB",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Apa nama program pelatihan pebalap muda (dibawah 14 tahun) yang dilakukan PT Astra Honda Motor?",
        optionA: "Astra Honda Racing School",
        optionB: "Astra Honda Talent Academy",
        optionC: "Astra Honda Racing Academy",
        optionD: "Honda Junior Talent",
        correctOption: "optionA",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang berkompetisi di CEV Moto 3 Junior World Championship 2021?",
        optionA: "Adenanta Putra",
        optionB: "Mario Suryo Aji",
        optionC: "Irfan Ardiansyah",
        optionD: "Rheza Danica",
        correctOption: "optionB",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang berkompetisi di kejurnas motocross kelas MX2 2021?",
        optionA: "Delvintor Alfarizi",
        optionB: "Mario Suryo Aji",
        optionC: "Rheza Danica",
        optionD: "Lucky Hendriansya",
        correctOption: "optionA",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang berkompetisi di Thailand Talent Cup 2021?",
        optionA: "Chessy Meilandri & Mario Suryo Aji",
        optionB: "Veda Ega Pratama & Herlian Dandi",
        optionC: "Chessy Meilandri & Veda Ega Pratama",
        optionD: "Herlian Dandi & Arzyan Dheyo",
        correctOption: "optionC",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang berkompetisi di Asia Talent Cup 2021?",
        optionA: "Herjun Atna Firdaus",
        optionB: "Azryan Dheyo & Herlian Dandi",
        optionC: "Fadillah Arbi Aditama",
        optionD: "Semua benar",
        correctOption: "optionD",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang berkompetisi di Asia Road Racing Champhionship Kelas SS600 2021?",
        optionA: "Rheza Danica & Irfan Ardiansya",
        optionB: "Lucky Hendriansya & Rheza Danica",
        optionC: "Mario Suryo Aji & Irfan Ardiansya",
        optionD: "Semua salah",
        correctOption: "optionA",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang berkompetisi di Asia Road Racing Champhionship Kelas AP250 2021?",
        optionA: "M. Adenanta Putra",
        optionB: "Lucky Hendriansya",
        optionC: "Herjun Atna Firdaus",
        optionD: "Semua benar",
        correctOption: "optionD",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/pembinaan-berjenjang-ahm-siap-antar-pembalap-muda-harumkan-bangsa-di-2021' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question: "Apa julukan yang dimiliki Mario Suryo Aji?",
        optionA: "Fantastic Mario",
        optionB: "Super Mario",
        optionC: "Mario Man",
        optionD: "Amazing Mario",
        correctOption: "optionB",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/riders/super-mario'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/riders/super-mario' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Berapa posisi yang diraih Mario Suryo Aji pada balap seri perdana CEV Moto3 Junior World Championship 2021?",
        optionA: "Ke-2",
        optionB: "Ke-7",
        optionC: "Ke-4",
        optionD: "Ke-6",
        correctOption: "optionC",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/nyaris-raih-podium-mario-finish-posisi-4-di-cev-estoril'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/nyaris-raih-podium-mario-finish-posisi-4-di-cev-estoril' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Di Sirkuit apa Mario Suryo Aji untuk pertama kali mendapatkan pole position pada ajang CEV Moto3 2021?",
        optionA: "Sirkuit Le Mans",
        optionB: "Sirkuit Aragon",
        optionC: "Sirkuit Jerez",
        optionD: "Sirkuit Catalunya",
        correctOption: "optionD",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/tempati-pole-position-di-cev-barcelona-mario-jalani-balapan-dengan-gigih'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/tempati-pole-position-di-cev-barcelona-mario-jalani-balapan-dengan-gigih' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Berapa jumlah musim yang sudah dijalani Mario Suryo Aji di kompetisi CEV Moto3 Junior World Championsip?",
        optionA: "1 Musim",
        optionB: "2 Musim",
        optionC: "3 Musim",
        optionD: "4 Musim",
        correctOption: "optionC",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/optimis-mario-siap-hadapi-musim-ketiga-fim-cev'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/optimis-mario-siap-hadapi-musim-ketiga-fim-cev' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang berhasil mewakili Indonesia di Grand Prix Moto2 pada tahun 2020?",
        optionA: "Andi Gilang",
        optionB: "Gerry Salim",
        optionC: "Mario Suryo Aji ",
        optionD: "Semua Benar",
        correctOption: "optionA",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/kebanggaan-bangsa-andi-gilang-membalap-semusim-penuh-di-gp-moto2-2020-1'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/kebanggaan-bangsa-andi-gilang-membalap-semusim-penuh-di-gp-moto2-2020-1' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Rekor apa yang berhasil diraih AHRT dalam kompetisi ARRC tahun 2019?",
        optionA: "Empat kali juara umum team AP250",
        optionB: "Tiga kali juara umum team AP250",
        optionC: "Dua kali juara umum team AP250",
        optionD: "Semua Salah",
        correctOption: "optionB",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/ahrt-persembahkan-rekor-baru-di-balap-asia-1'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/ahrt-persembahkan-rekor-baru-di-balap-asia-1' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang meraih juara di kompetisi ARRC AP250 pada tahun 2018?",
        optionA: "Andi Gilang",
        optionB: "Irfan Ardiansyah",
        optionC: "Rheza Danica",
        optionD: "Gerry Salim",
        correctOption: "optionC",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/astra-honda-racing-team-pertahankan-gelar-asia-production-250cc-berkat-kemenangan-rheza-danica-1'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/astra-honda-racing-team-pertahankan-gelar-asia-production-250cc-berkat-kemenangan-rheza-danica-1' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang sekaligus menjadi pebalap Indonesia pertama yang menjadi juara di ARRC AP250?",
        optionA: "Gerry Salim",
        optionB: "Mario Suryo Aji",
        optionC: "Andi Gilang",
        optionD: "Rheza Danica",
        correctOption: "optionA",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.instagram.com/p/BcMQdQfAyN3/?utm_medium=copy_link/'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.instagram.com/p/BcMQdQfAyN3/embed/captioned' allowtransparency='true' allowfullscreen='true' frameborder='0' height='900' data-instgrm-payload-id='instagram-media-payload-0' scrolling='no' style='background: white; max-width: 540px; width: calc(100% - 2px); border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid rgb(219, 219, 219); box-shadow: none; display: block; margin: 0px 0px 12px; min-width: 326px; padding: 0px;'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Siapa pebalap AHRT yang meraih juara di kompetisi nasional Motocross MX2 2019?",
        optionA: "Andi Gilang",
        optionB: "Delvintor Alfarizi",
        optionC: "Irfan Ardiansyah",
        optionD: "Rheza Danica",
        correctOption: "optionB",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.instagram.com/p/B5h08zdAzx7/?utm_medium=copy_link'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.instagram.com/p/B5h08zdAzx7/embed/captioned' allowtransparency='true' allowfullscreen='true' frameborder='0' height='930' data-instgrm-payload-id='instagram-media-payload-0' scrolling='no' style='background: white; max-width: 540px; width: calc(100% - 2px); border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid rgb(219, 219, 219); box-shadow: none; display: block; margin: 0px 0px 12px; min-width: 326px; padding: 0px;'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Apa tipe motor yang digunakan pembalap AHRT dalam menjuarai kompetisi ARRC AP250 tahun 2017 dan 2018?",
        optionA: "CBR150R",
        optionB: "CB150R",
        optionC: "CBR250RR",
        optionD: "CBR1000RR",
        correctOption: "optionC",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.instagram.com/p/CLtN7fYg4c4/?utm_medium=copy_link'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.instagram.com/p/CLtN7fYg4c4/embed/captioned' allowtransparency='true' allowfullscreen='true' frameborder='0' height='1380' data-instgrm-payload-id='instagram-media-payload-0' scrolling='no' style='background: white; max-width: 540px; width: calc(100% - 2px); border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid rgb(219, 219, 219); box-shadow: none; display: block; margin: 0px 0px 12px; min-width: 326px; padding: 0px;'></iframe>"
    },

    {
        question:
            "Apa tipe motor yang digunakan Delvintor Alfarizi dalam menjuarai kompetisi nasional Motocross MX2 2019?",
        optionA: "CRF150L",
        optionB: "CRF250 RALLY",
        optionC: "CRF1000L",
        optionD: "CRF250R",
        correctOption: "optionD",
        clueLink:
            "<a href='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/penampilan-perdana-astra-honda-racing-team-di-kejurnas-motocross-2019'> Klik Disini</a>",
        clueiFrame:
            "<iframe src='https://www.astra-honda.com/article/penampilan-perdana-astra-honda-racing-team-di-kejurnas-motocross-2019' style='display: block; width: 100%; height:75vh; border: none; overflow-y: auto; overflow-x: hidden;' frameborder='0' marginheight='0' marginwidth='0' width='100%' height='100%' scrolling='auto' allowfullscreen='true'></iframe>"
    }
];

let shuffledQuestions = []; //empty array to hold shuffled selected questions

function handleQuestions() {
    //function to shuffle and push 10 questions to shuffledQuestions array
    while (shuffledQuestions.length <= 4) {
        const random = questions[Math.floor(Math.random() * questions.length)];
        if (!shuffledQuestions.includes(random)) {
            shuffledQuestions.push(random);
        }
    }
}

let questionNumber = 1;
let playerScore = 0;
let wrongAttempt = 0;
let indexNumber = 0;

// function for displaying next question in the array to dom
function NextQuestion(index) {
    handleQuestions();
    const currentQuestion = shuffledQuestions[index];
    document.getElementById("question-number").innerHTML = questionNumber;
    document.getElementById("player-score").innerHTML = playerScore;
    document.getElementById("display-question").innerHTML =
        currentQuestion.question;
    document.getElementById("option-one-label").innerHTML =
        currentQuestion.optionA;
    document.getElementById("option-two-label").innerHTML =
        currentQuestion.optionB;
    document.getElementById("option-three-label").innerHTML =
        currentQuestion.optionC;
    document.getElementById("option-four-label").innerHTML =
        currentQuestion.optionD;
    document.getElementById("clue-iframe-label").innerHTML =
        currentQuestion.clueiFrame;
    // document.getElementById("clue-link-label").innerHTML = currentQuestion.clueLink;
}

function checkForAnswer() {
    const currentQuestion = shuffledQuestions[indexNumber]; //gets current Question
    const currentQuestionAnswer = currentQuestion.correctOption; //gets current Question's answer
    const options = document.getElementsByName("option"); //gets all elements in dom with name of 'option' (in this the radio inputs)
    let correctOption = null;

    options.forEach(option => {
        if (option.value === currentQuestionAnswer) {
            //get's correct's radio input with correct answer
            correctOption = option.labels[0].id;
        }
    });

    //checking to make sure a radio input has been checked or an option being chosen
    if (
        options[0].checked === false &&
        options[1].checked === false &&
        options[2].checked === false &&
        options[3].checked == false
    ) {
        document.getElementById("option-modal").style.display = "flex";
    }

    //checking if checked radio button is same as answer
    options.forEach(option => {
        if (option.checked === true && option.value === currentQuestionAnswer) {
            document.getElementById(correctOption).style.backgroundColor =
                "green";
            playerScore++;
            indexNumber++;
            //set to delay question number till when next question loads
            setTimeout(() => {
                questionNumber++;
            }, 1000);
        } else if (option.checked && option.value !== currentQuestionAnswer) {
            const wrongLabelId = option.labels[0].id;
            document.getElementById(wrongLabelId).style.backgroundColor = "red";
            document.getElementById(correctOption).style.backgroundColor =
                "green";
            wrongAttempt++;
            indexNumber++;
            //set to delay question number till when next question loads
            setTimeout(() => {
                questionNumber++;
            }, 1000);
        }
    });
}

//called when the next button is called
function handleNextQuestion() {
    checkForAnswer();
    unCheckRadioButtons();
    //delays next question displaying for a second
    setTimeout(() => {
        if (indexNumber <= 4) {
            NextQuestion(indexNumber);
        } else {
            handleEndGame();
        }
        resetOptionBackground();
    }, 1000);
}

//sets options background back to null after display the right/wrong colors
function resetOptionBackground() {
    const options = document.getElementsByName("option");
    options.forEach(option => {
        document.getElementById(option.labels[0].id).style.backgroundColor = "";
        document.getElementById(option.labels[0].id).style.color = "black";
    });
}

// unchecking all radio buttons for next question(can be done with map or foreach loop also)
function unCheckRadioButtons() {
    const options = document.getElementsByName("option");
    for (let i = 0; i < options.length; i++) {
        options[i].checked = false;
    }
}

// function for when all questions being answered
function handleEndGame() {
    const playerGrade = (playerScore / 5) * 100;

    if (playerGrade == 100) {
        $.ajax({
            method: "GET",
            crossDomain: true,
            crossOrigin: true,
            async: true,
            contentType: "application/json",
            headers: {
                "Access-Control-Allow-Methods": "*",
                "Access-Control-Allow-Credentials": true,
                "Access-Control-Allow-Headers":
                    "Access-Control-Allow-Headers, Origin, X-Requested-With, Content-Type, Accept, Authorization",
                "Access-Control-Allow-Origin": "*",
                "Control-Allow-Origin": "*",
                "cache-control": "no-cache",
                "Content-Type": "application/json"
            },
            url: "/get-trivia",
            success: function(resp) {
                console.log("Respond was: ", resp);
                $(".modaltitletrivia").text("Selamat !!");
                $(".textfinishtrivia").text(resp.response);
                if (resp.status == 1) {
                    document.getElementById(
                        "triviaredirect"
                    ).innerHTML = `<a href="user" type="button" class="btn btn-secondary">Oke</a>`;
                } else {
                    document.getElementById(
                        "triviaredirect"
                    ).innerHTML = `<a type="button" class="btn btn-secondary" data-bs-dismiss="modal">Oke</a>`;
                }
            },
            error: function(request, status, error) {
                console.log("Respond was: ", resp);
                $(".textfinishtrivia").text(resp.response);
            }
        });
    } else {
        $(".modaltitletrivia").text("Coba Ulangi !!");
        document.getElementById(
            "triviaredirect"
        ).innerHTML = `<a href="javascript: void(0)" onclick="closeScoreModal()" data-bs-dismiss="modal" type="button" class="btn btn-secondary">Oke</a>`;
    }

    const myModal = new bootstrap.Modal(
        document.getElementById("score-modal"),
        {
            backdrop: "static",
            keyboard: false
        }
    );
    myModal.show();

    //data to display to score board
    document.getElementById("wrong-answers").innerHTML = wrongAttempt;
    document.getElementById("right-answers").innerHTML = playerScore;
}

//closes score modal and resets game
function closeScoreModal() {
    questionNumber = 1;
    playerScore = 0;
    wrongAttempt = 0;
    indexNumber = 0;
    shuffledQuestions = [];
    NextQuestion(indexNumber);
}

//function to close warning modal
function closeOptionModal() {
    document.getElementById("option-modal").style.display = "none";
}
